something a lot deeper
there that you think looks
like, oh my God, wow,
I want to be them.
No, there's always something
that, you know, I kind of
like feel a bit for them.
Cause I'm like, there's a
reason they're seeking the
validation, the attention.
And I think that we need to
recognize that as individuals.
We don't have to be the
loudest in the room to be
the most confident at all.
Yeah, absolutely.
And just to kind of circle
back to your album of wins,
I'm glad you brought up
for the less visual people.
because I think I'm more
like written word style.
I have an Excel sheet, which
is very corporate of me.
But it's just because it's
kind of tied in with a
couple other things I'm
tracking, so to speak.
But I have like a wins list.
And so whenever something
happens big or small
doesn't matter.
I'll put it on the list.
And again, it's something I
can go back and reflect on.
And the best part about
doing this, whether you pick